# question_data = [
#     {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
# ]

import html

question_data = {"response_code": 0, "results": [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Unturned originally started as a Roblox game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                                       "question": "The song &quot;Mystery Train&quot; was released by artist &quot;Little Junior&#039;s Blue Flames&quot; in 1953.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "In Scandinavian languages, the letter &Aring; means river.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Vehicles",
                                       "question": "In 1993 Swedish car manufacturer Saab experimented with replacing the steering wheel with a joystick in a Saab 9000.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The chemical element Lithium is named after the country of Lithuania.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Mythology",
                                      "question": "Rannamaari was a sea demon that haunted the people of the Maldives and had to be appeased monthly with the sacrifice of a virgin girl.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
     "question": "In the comic book &quot;Archie&quot;, Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History",
     "question": "The Kingdom of Prussia briefly held land in Estonia.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Geography",
                                      "question": "The two largest ethnic groups of Belgium are Flemish and Walloon. ",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "This is the correct spelling of &quot;Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
     "question": "L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;The Sims&quot; series, the most members in a household you can have is 8.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The names of Roxas&#039;s Keyblades in Kingdom Hearts are &quot;Oathkeeper&quot; and &quot;Oblivion&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Danganronpa 2: Goodbye Despair featured all of the surviving students from the first game.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Minecraft&quot;, gold tools are faster than diamond tools.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Books",
                                       "question": "Harry Potter was born on July 31st, 1980.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Politics",
     "question": "George Clinton, Vice President of the United States (1805-1812), is an ancestor of President Bill Clinton.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
     "question": "The board game Go has more possible legal positions than the number of atoms in the visible universe.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The value of one Calorie is different than the value of one calorie.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
                                       "question": "If you could fold a piece of paper in half 50 times, its&#039; thickness will be 3\/4th the distance from the Earth to the Sun.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Computers",
     "question": "The T-Mobile Sidekick smartphone is a re-branded version of the Danger Hiptop.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The Paradox Interactive game &quot;Stellaris&quot; was released in 2016.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
                                       "question": "It was once believed that injecting shark cartilage into people would prevent them from contracting cancer.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Art",
     "question": "The Statue of Liberty&#039;s official name is &ldquo;Liberty Enlightening the World&rdquo;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Politics",
     "question": "Joko Widodo has appeared in the cover of a TIME magazine.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
                                       "question": "The Klingon home planet is Qo&#039;noS.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                       "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "&quot;Cube&quot;, &quot;Cube 2: Hypercube&quot; and &quot;Cube Zero&quot; were directed by the same person.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "&quot;Number 16 Bus Shelter&quot; was a child&#039;s name that was approved by the New Zealand government.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The band STRFKR was also briefly known as Pyramiddd.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The first &quot;Metal Gear&quot; game was released for the PlayStation 1.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "The protagonist in &quot;Humanity Has Declined&quot; has no discernable name and is simply referred to as &#039;I&#039; for most of the series.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Call Of Duty: World At War&quot;, the first appearance of the &quot;PPSH-41&quot; in &quot;Zombies&quot; was in the map &quot;Der Riese&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History",
     "question": "The fourth funnel of the RMS Titanic was fake designed to make the ship look more powerful and symmetrical.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Portal 2&quot;, Cave Johnson started out Aperture Science as a shower curtain company.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History",
     "question": "Japan was part of the Allied Powers during World War I.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Geography",
                                       "question": "Only one country in the world starts with the letter Q.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "All of these maps were in &quot;Tom Clancy&#039;s Rainbow Six Siege&quot; on its initial release: House, Clubhouse, Border, Consulate.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Books",
     "question": "In Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, Hermione destroyed the fourth Horcrux by stabbing it with the Sword of Gryffindor.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "The character Plum from &quot;No Game No Life&quot; is a girl.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
                                      "question": "The binary number &quot;101001101&quot; is equivalent to the Decimal number &quot;334&quot;",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "Throughout the entirety of &quot;Dragon Ball Z&quot;, Goku only kills two characters: a miniboss named Yakon and Kid Buu.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "Janus was the Roman god of doorways and passageways.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Computers",
                                       "question": "DHCP stands for Dynamic Host Configuration Port.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Musicals &amp; Theatres",
     "question": "The protagonist&#039;s names in &#039;Who&#039;s Afraid of Virginia Woolf&#039;, George and Martha, were derived from George Washington and his wife.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Politics",
     "question": "Nazi Germany surrendered on Harry Truman&#039;s birthday while he was president.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Peke is considered a female robot.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History",
                                       "question": "The Battle of Trafalgar took place on October 23rd, 1805",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The singer Billie Holiday was also known as &quot;Lady Day&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Vehicles",
                                       "question": "The term &quot;GTO&quot; was originated by Ferrari?",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The retail disc of Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater 5 only comes with the tutorial.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]}

def decode_question_data(data):
    for result in data["results"]:
        result["question"] = html.unescape(result["question"])
    return data

decoded_question_data = decode_question_data(question_data)
decoded_question_data = [{"text": question["question"], "answer": question["correct_answer"]} for question in question_data["results"]]
question_data = decoded_question_data


